Guide to the Cornell University Hospital for Animals records, 1979-2005
Cornell University Hospital for Animals records, 1979-2005
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Cornell University Hospital for Animals Records, 1979-2005
24-06-3313
Cornell University, College of Veterinary Medicine. Cornell University Hospital for Animals
1.3 cubic ft.
Minutes, handbooks, videocassettes.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Minutes of the Hospital Board and Section Chief meetings, as well as the annual "Student Protocol," a handbook of policies and procedures for fourth year DVM students, and one videocassette from the Cornell University College of Veterinary Medicine Equine Performance Testing Unit. Also brochures from the hospital.
ORGANIZATIONAL HISTORY
The Cornell University Hospital for Animals (CUHA) is a unit of the Cornell University College of Veterinary Medicine. It comprises the Companion Animal Hospital, the Equine Hospital and the Farm Animal Hospital. Specialized units within the hospital include Wildlife and Exotic Animal Medicine, Ambulatory and Production Medicine, and Behavioral Medicine. It is currently housed in the Veterinary Education Center, which was opened in 1996. It was formerly named the Cornell University Veterinary Medical Teaching Hospital, but was renamed in 2000.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
This collection includes minutes of the Hospital Board and Section Chief meetings, as well as the annual "Student Protocol," a handbook of policies and procedures for fourth year DVM students, and one videocassette from the Cornell University College of Veterinary Medicine Equine Performance Testing Unit. Also brochures from the hospital.
Also photographs and slides.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Cornell University--College of Veterinary Medicine--Cornell University Hospital for Animals.
Subjects:
Veterinary medicine--Study and teaching.; Veterinary hospitals--New York (State)
Form and Genre Terms:
Photographs.; Slides (photographs).
INFORMATION FOR USERS
SERIES LIST
Series I. Hospital Board Meeting Minutes
Series II. Section Chief Meeting Minutes
Series III. Student Protocol
*The Student Protocol handbooks have been alternately called the "Student Procedure and Policy Manual" and "Student Responsibilities and General Information."
Series IV. Miscellaneous
Series V. Photographs and Slides
Box 2
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. Hospital Board Meeting Minutes
  - Minutes, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Minutes, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Minutes, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Minutes, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Minutes, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Minutes, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Minutes, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Minutes, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Minutes, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous Material, 1994, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Minutes, agendas, etc., 2004, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Series II. Section Chief Meeting Minutes
  - Minutes, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Minutes, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Minutes, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Minutes, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Series III. Student Protocol
  - Student Procedure and Policy Manual, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Student Procedure and Policy Manual, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Student Procedure and Policy Manual, 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Student Procedure and Policy Manual, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Student Responsibilities and General Information, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Student Responsibilities and General Information, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Student Protocol, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Student Protocol, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Student Protocol, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Student Protocol, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Student Protocol, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Student Protocol, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Student Protocol, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Student Protocol, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Student Protocol, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Student Protocol, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Series IV. Student Miscellaneous
  - Brochures, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - VHS Tape: Cornell University College of Veterinary Medicine Equine Performance Testing Unit, n.d.; V-6839 (Box 1)
  - Hospital Protocol (folder 1), ca. 1985 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Hospital Protocol (folder 2), ca. 1985 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Resident and Intern Lists, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Cancer Program, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Cornell at Saratoga - Photos, 1999-2000 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Cornell Companions Program, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Diversity Postcard Project, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Ambulatory Clinic Cook Book, no date (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Series V. Photographs and Slides
  - Continuing Education - slides, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Slides and Photographs, 1974-2002 (Box 2, Folder 1-5)